Finding Aid for Office of the Vice President and Secretary of the University (University of Michigan) records, 1935-2007
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files
  - General Files
    - National Science Foundation (NSF) Advance, 2001-2005 (Box 32)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF) Advance -- Institutional Transformation Awards Program, 2001, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF) Advance -- U of Arizona Study on Equity, 2001 (Box 32)
    - Office of Academic Affairs, 1969-1989 (Box 32)
    - Office of Academic Affairs, 2004-2005 (Box 32)
    - Office of the Executive Vice President and CFO, 1999-2004 (Box 32)
    - Office of Minority Affairs, 1986-1988 (Box 32)
    - Office of Student Services, 1965-1990, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Office of the Vice President for Communications, 2000-2002 (Box 33)
    - Office of the Vice President for Research, 1998-2006 (Box 33)
    - Office of the Vice President for Research, 1999-2002 (Box 33)
    - Open Meetings, 1995 (Box 33)
    - Open Meetings, 1995-1997 (Box 33)
    - Open Meetings Act, 1976-1993 (Box 33)
    - Open Meetings Act, 1977-1995 (Box 33)
    - Outstanding Achievement Awards, 1958-1991 (Box 33)
    - Packard Hangar -- Willow Run, 1990-1993 (Box 33)
    - Palestinian Conference, 2002 (Box 33)
    - Parking -- U of M, 1975-2002 (Box 33)
    - Peace Corps 20th Anniversary Photo, 1980 (Box 33)
    - Penn State -- Big Ten, 1990 (Box 33)
    - Phoenix Memorial Laboratory, 1992 (Box 33)
    - Photographs, circa 1987 (Box 33)
    - Plant Operations, 1988 (Box 33)
    - Policy on Disruption of Student Activities, 1988-1992 (Box 33)
    - Policy on Student Sponsored Social Events, 1990 (Box 33)
    - Political Correctness, 1990-1991 (Box 33)
    - Population Planning and International Health, 1977-1993 (Box 33)
    - Press Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 33)
    - Printing Services, 2002 (Box 33)
    - Professorships, 1973-1992 (Box 33)
    - Proposed Legislation, 1959-1986, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Psychology Honors Research Program, 1999-2004 (Box 34)
    - Public Comments, 1999-2002 (Box 34)
    - Public Forums, 1995 (Box 34)
    - Public Interest Research Group in Michigan (PIRGIM), 1972-1988 (Box 34)
    - Public Safety, 1996 (Box 34)
    - Public Service Database, 1988 (Box 34)
    - Purchasing Ethics and Policies Report, 2004 (Box 34)
    - Racism/Human Relations, 1987-1991 (Box 34)
    - Racist Incidents -- UM, 1987 (Box 34)
    - Rackham Building, 1993 (Box 34)
    - Rackham School of Graduate Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 34)
    - Rare Isotope Accelerator, 2003 (Box 34)
    - Reaccreditation Notes (Tedesco), 1999-2000 (Box 34)
    - Reach Out Program, 2002 (Box 34)
    - Real Estate Policies, 2004-2005 (Box 34)
    - Reconciliation -- Nickerson, Markert, Davis, 1954-1998 (Box 34)
    - Recycling, 1987-1989 (Box 34)
    - Reeves, Fred, 1995 (Box 34)
    - Regents' Award for Distinguished Public Service, 1999-2003 (Box 34)
    - Regents' Award for Distinguished Public Service, 2004-2006 (Box 34)
    - Regents Merit Scholarship, 2003-2006 (Box 34)
    - Research, 1972-1994, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Research Club, 1998 (Box 35)
    - Research Restrictions Strategy, 2003 (Box 35)
    - Residential Life Initiatives, 2001-2004 (Box 35)
    - Retirement Bylaw, 1923-1995 (Box 35)
    - Retreat -- Future of the Faculty, 1998 (Box 35)
    - Rosenboom Case, 1987-1988 (Box 37)
      [CR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2088 ]
    - ROTC, 1997 (Box 35)
    - Royal Shakespeare Company, 2002 (Box 35)
    - Royal Shakespeare Media, 2001(includes cassette tape) (Box 35)
    - Russia (Staff Garnishment Case), 2001 (Box 35)
    - SACUA, 1961-1999 (Box 35)
    - SACUA, 1999-2004 (Box 35)
    - SACUA -- Intellectual Property, 2001 (Box 35)
    - Salary Studies, 1970-1984 (Box 35)
    - Sanchez, Sara, 2001 (Box 37)
    - Sarbanes-Oxley, 2004-2005 (Box 35)
    - Scholarships, 1989-1993 (Box 35)
    - School of Art, 1987-1991 (Box 35)
    - School of Dentistry, 1999-2005 (Box 35)
    - School of Education, 1969-1986 (Box 35)
    - School of Natural Resources and Environment, 1975-1993 (Box 36)
    - School of Nursing, 1975-1986 (Box 36)
    - School of Nursing, 2002-2005 (includes CD-ROM), 1 optical disks CD-ROMs (Box 36)
    - Science Article -- Complex Systems, 1999 (Box 36)
    - Security and Security Clearance, 1979-1994 (Box 36)
    - Sesquicentennial Award Recipients, 1963-1967 (Box 36)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1989-1991 (Box 36)
    - Shapiro, Harold T., 1980-1988 (Box 36)
    - Simpson Memorial Institute, 1988 (Box 36)
    - Solomon Amendment, 1983-1984 (Box 36)
    - State Building Authority Leases, 1992 (Box 36)
    - State of Michigan, 1975-1987 (Box 36)
    - Student Publications Board, 1993-1997 (Box 36)
    - Student Fees, 1962-1998 (Box 36)
    - Students for a New Michigan Image, 1989 (Box 36)
    - Students -- General, 1967-1970 (Box 36)
    - Symposiums/Seminars -- General, 1999-2001 (Box 36)
    - Telecommunications Bond, 1984 (Box 36)
    - Telecommunications Systems, 1984-1989 (Box 36)
    - Tenure, 1992 (Box 36)
    - Tenure Document, 2001 (Box 36)
    - "The University of Michigan" Publication, undated (Box 36)
    - Tobacco Divestment Project, 1992 (Box 36)
    - Total Quality Management (M-Quality), 1993 (Box 36)
    - Trademark Audit, 2000, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Transcriber Sales and Service, 1990-1992 (Box 36)
    - Travel, 1954-1990 (Box 36)
    - Tuition Differentials, 1983-1996 (Box 36)
    - UM Administration-City of Ann Arbor Softball Game, 1990-1996 (Box 36)
    - UM Center for Child and Family, 1991 (Box 36)
    - UM Historical File, 1959-1980 (Box 36)
    - UM Profile, 1989-2000 (Box 36)
    - UM Schools and Colleges Committee, 1969 (Box 36)
    - UM Websites, 1995-1998 (Box 36)
    - Union (AFSCME), 1966-1991, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - United Coalition Against Racism (UCAR), 1987 (Box 36)
    - Universitas 21, 2000 (Box 36)
    - Universities (other), 1991 (Box 36)
    - University Judicial System, 1971-1979 (Box 36)
    - University Library, 1988-1989 (Box 36)
    - University of Michigan Press, 1984-1985 (Box 36)
    - University Policies, 1990 (Box 36)
    - University Publications -- Miscellaneous, undated (Box 36)
    - US News, 1990 (Box 36)
    - Vest, Charles M., 1989-1990 (Box 36)
    - Washtenaw County Board of Commissioners, 1991 (Box 36)
    - Wayne County General Hospital, 1983-1984 (Box 36)
    - Wayne State University, 1995-1996 (Box 36)
    - WCBN Radio, 1990-1991 (Box 36)
    - Wilson, Linda (OVPR), 1986-1989 (Box 36)
    - Womack, Farris W., 1988-1994 (Box 36)
    - "Women at the University of Michigan: A Statistical Report on the Status of Women, Students, Faculty and Staff on the Ann Arbor Campus," 1996 (Box 36)
    - Women Faculty, 1992 (Box 36)
    - "Women's Health: A Guide to Curricular Opportunities at the University of Michigan," 1996 (Box 36)
    - Woodridge, LTD and Whitehall, 1982 (Box 36)
    - World Cup Soccer Resolution, 1991 (Box 36)
    - Zarko, Chetly, 1995-1996
Secretary (University of Michigan) Collections, 1845-1953
Vice President of Government Relations (University of Michigan) records, 1960-1999
Board of Regents (University of Michigan) agendas, 1996-2007
Board of Regents (University of Michigan) records, 1817-2010
Assistant to the President (University of Michigan) records, 1913-1986